{
  "hardquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 36 ÷ 6?",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 56 ÷ 8?",
      "answer1": "7",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 45 ÷ 5?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "10",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 63 ÷ 7?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 ÷ 8?",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 72 ÷ 9?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 81 ÷ 9?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 90 ÷ 10?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "10",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 54 ÷ 6?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 40 ÷ 5?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "8"
    }
  ]
}
